http://www.fsbwc.com/about/privacy-security

Privacy & Security
What do First State Bank and Town & Country Insurance do with your personal information?
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social security number
Income
Account balances
Payment history
Credit history
Employment history
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers’ personal information to run their everyday business.  In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers’ personal information; the reasons First State Bank/T&C chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
For our everyday business purposes - Such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus.
Question:
Answer:
Do First State Bank and Town & Country Share this?
Yes
Can you limit this sharing?
No
For our marketing purposes - To offer our products and services to you.
Question:
Answer:
Do First State Bank and Town & Country Share this?
Yes
Can you limit this sharing?
No
For joint marketing with other financial companies
Question:
Answer:
Do First State Bank and Town & Country Share this?
No
Can you limit this sharing?
We don't share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - Information about your transactions and experiences
Question:
Answer:
Do First State Bank and Town & Country Share this?
No
Can you limit this sharing?
We don't share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes - Information about your creditworthiness
Question:
Answer:
Do First State Bank and Town & Country Share this?
No
Can you limit this sharing?
We don't share
For non-affiliates to market to you
Question:
Answer:
Do First State Bank and Town & Country Share this?
No
Can you limit this sharing?
We don't share
Questions?
Call 515-832-2520 or go to www.fsbwc.com or www.tcins.com
Who we are
Who is providing this notice? First State Bank and Town & Country Insurance (T&C)
What we do
How do First State Bank and T&C protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law.  These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How do First State Bank and T&C collect my personal information?
We also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus and other companies.
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
Sharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthiness
Affiliates from using your information to market to you
Sharing for nonaffiliates to market to you
State law and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
First State Bank and Town & Country Insurance have no affiliates.
Nonaffiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.
First State Bank and Town & Country Insurance do not share personal information with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.
Joint marketing
A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
First State Bank and Town & Country Insurance do not engage in joint marketing.
First State Bank's website is directed to a general audience. We do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from children on our site.
Approved July 2019
First State Bank — First for you!
© 2020 FSBWC. All rights reserved.
